[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":29502,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":34136,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":4852,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":38990,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":8623,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":47615,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1231,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":48847,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3058,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":51907,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1006,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":52914,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result .)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3864,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":56779,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1061,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":57843,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2363,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":60207,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because  1 + 1 =  2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1008,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":61215,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2220,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":63435,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":974,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":64411,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number,  and the n add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":1972,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":66383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":798,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":67182,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["3","4"],"rt":3503,"trial_type":"qu estion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":70687,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":751,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":71439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3522,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":74963,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1243,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":76207,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2200,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":78407,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":811,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":79219,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get y our resu lt.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2190,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":81411,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":771,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":82183,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":8998,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":91183,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 "},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":739683,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":830868,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":14419,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":845290,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7 -0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":62847,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":908138,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2354,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":910494,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1255,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":911750,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the invers e of 3 u nder +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2011,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":913762,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1079,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":914842,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1715,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":916558,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1063,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":917622,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":1994,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":919618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":84473,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":1004092,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":326721,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":1330814,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br />< br /> Ho wever, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":11535,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":1342350,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4923,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1347274,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":4883,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1352158,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4387,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1356546,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1371,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1357918,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator u nder +<s ub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2392,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1360311,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1138,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1361450,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":1999,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1363450,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1123,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1364574,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as  accurate ly as possible.","rt":439331,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1803906,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":10761,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1814668,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1888,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1816559,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2646,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1819205,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2749,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1821956,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["9","0"],"rt":4248,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1826205,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3350,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1829556,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2224,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1831781,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It is less than 9 so I keep the 5","response_history":["It is less than 9 so I keep the 5"],"rt":10986,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1842768,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It is more than 9 so I subtract 9 from 12","response_history":["It is more than 9 so I subtracyt","It is more than 9 so I subtracy","It is more than 9 so I subtract 9 from 12"],"rt":23362,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1866131,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in word s how yo u got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"I'm not sure. 0? ","response_history":["I'm not sure. 0? "],"rt":10424,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1876556,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"I have no idea. I didn't understand this portion.","response_history":["I have no idea. I du","I have no idea. I didn't understand this portion."],"rt":16274,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1892831,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"I'm not sure.","response_history":["I'm not sure."],"rt":6948,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1899781,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9?","response_history":["9?"],"rt":3774,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1903556,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6?","response_history":["6?"],"rt":5286,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1908843,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I have no idea","response_history":["I have no idea"],"rt":6012,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1914856,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Idk","response_history":["Idk"],"rt":3274,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1918131,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I dont know","response_history":["I dont knoiw","I dont know"],"rt":9547,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1927679,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't think so","response_history":["I don't think  so"],"rt":27951,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1955631,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":65252,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2020884,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+_n=n","response_history":["1=_n=","1=_n","1=_","1=","1=","1+=","1+-","1+_n=n"],"rt":29159,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2050044,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Wha t is the  formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I have no clue. I don't even understand what you're asking. I am so honestly lost now. I understood the first part of the lesson but after that I just don't get it. I am so terrible at math terminology. I'm sorry.","response_history":["I have no clue. I don't even understand what you're asking. I am so honestly lost that ","I have no clue. I don't even understand what you're asking. I am so honestly lost that","I have no clue. I don't even understand what you're asking. I am so honestly lost tha","I have no clue. I don't even understand what you're asking. I am so honestly lost th","I have no clue. I don't even understand what you're asking. I am so honestly lost t","I have no clue. I don't even understand what you're asking. I am so honestly lost now. I feel","I have no clue. I don't  even un derstand what you're asking. I am so honestly lost now. I fee","I have no clue. I don't even understand what you're asking. I am so honestly lost now. I fe","I have no clue. I don't even understand what you're asking. I am so honestly lost now. I f","I have no clue. I don't even understand what you're asking. I am so honestly lost now. I understood the first part or","I have no clue. I don't even understand what you're asking. I am so honestly lost now. I understood the first part of the lesson but at","I have no clue. I don't even understand what you're asking. I am so honestly lost now. I understood the first part of the lesson but after that I a","I have no clue. I don't even understand what you're asking. I am so honestly lost now. I understood the first part of the lesson but after that I just don't get it. I am so terrible at math terminology. I'm sorry."],"rt":40712,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2090757,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I don't know","response_history":["I don't klnow","I don't klno","I don't kln","I don't kl","I don't know"],"rt":8499,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2099257,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":7527,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2106785,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":2923,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2109709,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":2494,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2112205,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I'm not sure.","response_history":["I'm not sure."],"rt":9851,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2122057,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":5318,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2127378,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I'm not sure.","response_history":["I'm not sure."],"rt":3192,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2130570,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an  element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":3394,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2133966,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1531,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2135498,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"25","response_history":["25"],"rt":2071,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2137570,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":3091,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2140662,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Basic algebra  in high school is the last I remember and I cannot complete the coursework today. ","response_history":["Basic A","Basic algebra  in high school is the last I remember and I cannot complete the coursework today. S","Basic algebra  in high school is the last I rememb er and I  cannot complete the coursework today. "],"rt":19232,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2159895,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3778,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2163674,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, reme mber and  understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":2483,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2166158,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4283,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2170442,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat"],"rt":3983,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2174426,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":3339,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2177766,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2431,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2180198,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":3171,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2183370,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","response_history":["no"],"rt":2436,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2185807,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm sorry that I couldn't do very well. ","response_history":["I'm sorry that I couldn't do very well. I","I'm sorry that I couldn't do very well. "],"rt":9324,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2195132,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]